I only told you about perfect development,
私は完璧な発達についてのみ話しました。
because I want to put you on the perfect body.
なぜなら、あなたを完璧な体に乗せたいからです。
We're going to do a practice together now on the fibula,
今から腓骨で一緒に練習をします。
to search until we have a sensation of liquid.
液体の感覚が得られるまで探します。
The bone here, and the bone here, and we're going to take it like this.
ここにある骨とここにある骨をこのように持ちます。
You wait for the neutral, you take the fibula a bit like you would take a
中立を待ち、大きな羽を持つように腓骨を少し持ちます。
large feather.
大きな羽。
You observe it in that.
その中で観察します。
position, the structure of the bone, but simply first on the density,
骨の位置、構造ですが、まず密度についてです。
that is
つまり、
to say that first you have to adjust well, you let the bone little
まず、うまく調整する必要があります。骨を少しずつ動かして、
by little find its
その
perfect spatial position, you place yourself well on the microcrystalline field, the
完璧な空間的位置を見つけさせます。微結晶の場にしっかりと身を置くと、
response will be a level of heat that will change, thermodynamic that changes,
熱のレベルが変化し、熱力学が変化します。
now you will put yourself on a cellular consciousness,
今、あなたは細胞意識に身を置きます。
finally you take a bunch of cells and then you put yourself on a
最終的に、あなたは細胞の束を取り、分子意識に身を置きます。
molecular consciousness.
分子意識。
It's like you have to try
それは、あなたが試すべきことのようです。
to descend
降りていくこと。
into a depth of perception.
知覚の深みへ。
But you let yourself
しかし、あなたは自分自身を委ねます。
be taken by the
に捕らえられます。
primary respiration. Don't forget
一次呼吸。忘れないでください。
that you need your neutral and let the neutral of the person
あなたの中立が必要であり、その人の中立が成熟するのを待つ必要があります。
mature. There is no
その人の中立が成熟するのを待つ必要があります。
maturation of the neutral
中立の成熟はありません。
on both sides.
両側で。
I call my friend
私は友人を呼びます。
and ask him to place himself at the level
そして、頭蓋底のレベルに身を置くように頼みます。
of the base of the skull.
頭蓋底のレベルに。
So the bone is fluid, it is in the fluid body little by little.
したがって、骨は流動的であり、徐々に流動的な体の中にあります。
It's good to discover this through this bone, because it's a membranous bone.
この骨を通してこれを発見するのは良いことです。なぜなら、それは膜性の骨だからです。
It's a bone that really comes from a membrane that has gradually
それは、徐々に凝縮した膜から本当に来る骨です。
condensed.
凝縮しました。
It's already membranous embryonically.
それはすでにこれらの膜性の胚です。
Yes, no, even further, you go below the atomic plane and then you pass into the plane.
はい、いいえ、さらに遠く、原子の鉛の下に行き、その後、鉛の中に入ります。
vibratory and then you pass it to the luminous plane. Here we stayed on the molecular plane where you have the
振動の、そしてそれを光の平面に渡します。ここでは、H2Oの組み合わせがある分子の平面にとどまっています。
H2O combination.
H2Oの組み合わせ。